Hey. Hey. Hey.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey.
Hey. Hey. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wendy.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hello everyone. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Uh I'm so sorry. I'm so struggling here.
Uh to multitask. [laughter and gasps]
Uh once again, give me a minute.
This is my first time doing first collab
of the year and I'm struggling.
[laughter]
Okay, baby. My whole piece is lagging,
bro.
Hello, Dragonoser. Welcome in. Hello.
Hello.
Uh, okay. Wait.
Uh, we having technical difficulties
here. Let me
Hi, Michael Pnes. Let me know when
they're ready, then I'll uh show them.
Hi. Um, let me just speed on this.
Hi, M.
Okay.
Hello. Hello.
All
right. All right. Oh god.
So I'm so
my P is not handling streaming.
Okay. Wait. Um
Uh,
no. I don't need that.
okay.
[sighs and gasps]
I'll add the description of the kola one
by one. Okay. Uh, give me a minute.
Let me
slowly do that. Um,
hello kid.
Welcome. Welcome.
Hello. Happy new year. Happy new year to
you as well.
Happy new year. D.
Happy new year.
Today's a collab stream with a few
friends, a few INV YouTubers.
Uh they invited me for New Year's uh new
year by talking to them all. Sometimes
if there's no audience
>> bad when people stream and they're
talking in void [music] I'm like I want
to chat with you chat don't worry.
>> I can understand that.
>> Yeah having people it really helps I
guess.
>> Okay one question about models. How many
of you prefer life 2D more than 3D?
Avatar.
>> Uh, live is nice. I want to get 3D, man.
>> Yeah, live 2D is like really beautiful
and all that. You can do a lot of things
with live 2D one, but with 3D it's more
practical.
>> I guess
>> I don't know the word. For me, [music]
both are difficult choices for me.
>> And depends on the PC now. If your PC
can't handle it.
>> Yeah,
>> my PC cannot even handle. Okay. PNG.
What are you talking? [laughter]
>> So, if I say based on choices, not on
PC, of course, then I won't be able to
say my choices. I feel life today is
better because it has that real feeling
of YouTubers like it was the first.
Yeah. I mean, yeah, life 2 days is
crazy,
>> right? [clears throat]
>> Yeah.
>> But it is too much difficult to get a
life 2D model.
>> It's super expensive. [laughter]
>> Yeah, that's what I was saying.
>> For 3D, you need a good graphic card and
230 GB. Oh, yeah. True. and trackers as
well.
>> Okay. Next, next question. Next
question. Next, next.
>> Okay.
>> Uh, how many of you have played Gacha
games?
>> I have played it in the past.
>> Never.
>> Saw you playing
Jo I have seen I've seen Joik play a
lot.
>> I play and I stop after a while
>> after getting burnt out.
>> I have like recently started with Hong
Kai Star and yeah waves. So the question
is now most of you don't play gacha
games and the question is useless. Okay.
Do you prefer more adventure games or
horror [music] games like typical horror
or just action?
>> Advent adventure is adventure is good
for the heart.
>> Horror is good for the content.
>> Shooting game.
>> Oh, that is the best
>> shooting. I don't like shooting games.
>> If it's a battle royale, then it's uh I
don't know if you die. If you die a lot,
you'll feel sad. No, but that add
>> addiction will be there.
>> I don't like battle royale. I don't I
don't know [music] why.
>> Oh, I I don't like shooting games
because uh I always lose in them. So,
yeah.
>> The thing
the most sad part of it, I mean, it's
easy in adventure games. It's very hard
in like the shooting games. I I
>> for me it depends on my mood.
>> Oh,
>> as in
>> Okay,
I see. I see. Wait. Okay. One thing I
like this
>> since we are talking about so one
question. what advice [music]
you will give yourself that you like you
have done some mistake in 2025 but you
don't want to repeat in 2026 so yeah
>> nice question that
>> uh
>> let's start with surya you tell
>> for uh [music] a mistake that I don't
want to I want to be more disciplined
this time. I think I was really
undisiplined and unscheduled [music]
this year.
>> Yeah, I need to figure out how that
stuff works.
What about Kaid?
uh understand feelings and uh
uh decision making
uh or
I think it may
>> that's kind
for 26 I would say um I want to uh love
myself better and all that's one. Second
will be um uh choosing the good friends
and [music] keeping them close this
time. I made a mistake with that in
2025. So I wish to get that correctly in
2026 with boundaries and everything.
>> Yes. Yes. For me just I have to stop
using I have to stop changing my models
every second week.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, literally my interest so fast.
Like literally, I just changed my model
3D. I [music] got a new 3D model. I used
it for two streams and then I'm like, I
don't like this. I'll use another one.
>> It's okay.
>> Yeah.
And I need to be more consistent with
this because I really love to stream and
stuff like it gives me peace.
[clears throat]
>> A lot of stuff happened with you as
well, right? Meo, you were like I think
uh if I remember correctly, you were
going to stop streaming as well, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I was going to stop
streaming. Okay, let Okay, let me tell.
So basically I started streaming in I
just um yeah May right and Jonix helped
me a lot at that time. Yeah like I got
confidence while seeing him. So [music]
yeah in May I started and then I stopped
in August because
>> Hello Rishio 8610 welcome to the stream
>> like IRL stuff to face lot of stuff
right exams [music] and all studies and
everything then I stopped and then
recently I stopped for a few weeks
because of uh some thing that happened
with my 3D model like I had some uh I
had to face many things regarding my 3D
model.
>> Yeah.
>> What about you P? How was
the how was yours? Like you I think you
also face problems currently right about
the models and all that.
>> Yeah. Like recently.
Yeah. Tell about that. What happened
with your play store thing?
It's It's funny.
>> Wait, wait, wait. Kind your voice. Your
voice not coming.
>> Yeah, the Fuji tech is working but your
voice.
>> Yeah.
>> Hello. Hello.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's
>> coming. Can hear now.
>> Okay. Okay.
Tell
the Play [music] Store stuff that
happened.
Oh, I was asking that
I was asking uh the thing that happened
with your uh play store and all uh the
play store and everything.
What was the issue [music] this year was
full of issues?
>> Uh first time I started the video tubing
with the app called reality. [music]
Uh it's been so long. Uh
uh
I don't think
problem.
Oh. Uh that was like missing of webcam
or not working.
webcam.
Uh, you're asking.
>> Yeah.
Uh,
payment
historyudio.
Yes, that's great. That's great.
>> And Znex, any stuff that happened with
this year?
>> Wait, this year?
>> It [laughter] was
last year.
>> Last year, I guess. [laughter]
>> Oh, yeah.
I [clears throat] mean, if you're if
you're talking about model things,
right? Um,
>> no.
>> Ah. Oh, yeah. that stuff. Okay. Uh I I
will also make a detailed video on this
this year I think. But yeah, basically I
have to pay so much money
uh for my live duty now. Uh and I can't
even Oh, it's because no um I had like a
opportunity given like it was like an
agency and stuff and it was like a
startup and um they didn't know what
they're coming into like how expensive
YouTubing can be and everything. [music]
I was supposed to be their first talent
and stuff. Then in a way I had my model
uh they paid for the model and started
the commission. The art was done and
then they were like yeah we can't do
this uh we're going to pause it for a
while and they
uh started to focus on their parent
company and [music] stuff. Then I was
like patiently waiting for 6 to 8
months. Then I was like the artist
already did the model. No. And uh if the
agency is not going to continue if
there's if if it [music] will take like
5 years or 6 years to come back. No.
Isn't it better I take the model and get
out of there and try to fund it myself?
I thought of that. So
>> February of 2025 I was like okay I'm
going to do that. Then uh we had to do
like a uh like a agreement that I pay
the agency cuz they paid for the model.
No, the art.
>> Yeah. Uh like a yearly subscription kind
of thingy. I have to pay a little bit of
money. But then I realized for life duty
is so expensive.
>> Yeah. And for life duty is like uh
almost $1,000. That's like one lakh or
something. I don't know.
Yeah.
>> And I'm like, "Yeah, I'm never going to
see this model again." That's why I did
the Joon thingy.
And um even now I I only have a little
bit of uh I saved up only a little bit
so it won't No. So I hope one day I can
debut that model. Mhm.
But I'm at least glad that I have
something now. at least the PNG.
Uh the old models I can't use it due to
stuff which happened. [laughter]
I don't know if I can use it. So yeah,
2025 was rough.
Yeah,
>> it was
it was a messy year I would say, but we
got to learn a lot, I guess.
Yeah,
>> it was I would say that I think this
year first of all there was a lot of
political stuff then there was
geographical stuff then there was war
stuff I guess
>> and yeah it was a it was a different
kind of year uh and [music] now we have
stories that we survived wars for our
grandchildren I guess.
>> Mhm.
>> And uh for the V tubing I think finally
in India there has been a lot of people
coming. Yeah, it's been expensive.
People are making and there's a lot of
AI stuff happening now. AI game and
there's a lot of hate about that as
well. But I guess it's working right
and everyone is growing, everyone is
learning. There are rules not everyone
understand that. And [music] yeah, I
would say that I think the you have
stopped the subathon, right? Or are you
going to continue it later?
Uh, I don't know. I'm probably probably
not. I guess I I'm not sure.
>> Yeah, too much pain.
>> It was taxing. Yeah, [laughter] it was I
guess taxing.
>> Yeah,
this time I'll take it easy and chill
like I initially wanted to do. Now, have
fun with family this time.
>> Mhm.
>> Take [music] time out. What about you,
Kaid? Are there any new things except
for the beautiful model that will will
[music] be seen this year? Any plans?
Anything we can wait for, look forward
to?
>> I haven't planned anything yet, but I'm
hoping
finger crossed on that one. Yeah,
>> hopefully that works out. And uh
actually I was counting people. That's
not a good thing, but still. And I think
we can start on Among Us and all that
series together.
I think we have enough people, I guess.
>> Oh, Among Us. I missed that game. People
still play it? [laughter]
>> [gasps]
>> Yeah, it's still in uh in the UK and USA
there's still a lot of grace above that
game.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It also breaks friendship there.
[laughter]
>> Wait, but but it's paid in PC, right? I
can't play.
>> Yeah, it's like uh what is [music]
1307, I guess.
>> Yeah, but we can play on blue stack. You
can always uh play on blue stack. They
allow it.
>> Yeah,
>> the game developers itself says that you
can get it from the blue stack for free
if you want.
>> Okay, then I'm fine.
>> Okay. And I'm [music] fine.
>> Yeah,
>> it was fun. I can I have we can start
[music] different stuff. We can play
repo and all that. We have a lot of
content to make, I guess, this year.
Miko is on a break if anyone's
wondering. He'll be back in a second.
>> Okay.
>> Listening
on a Yeah.
>> H go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Then
continue. Continue.
>> It's
I just going to yap on the random stuff.
You have continue.
>> [clears throat]
>> I was going to ask like was there any
favorite games you guys um played in
2025 and [music] any Yeah. was there any
favorite games you liked in 2025 you
played on stream or uh off stream?
>> Uh mine [music] I think mine was a big
one. Uh,
mine Magic Chess was the I think my
[music] top tier game this year cuz I
went too crazy on that one I guess for
the TFT. I've been playing regional
tournaments and all that.
>> Oh,
>> yeah. I haven't been selected above two
top 2,000 people.
>> Yeah.
>> Welcome back.
>> What are you guys talking about? I'm
back.
>> Welcome. Uh, we were talking about your
favorite games you played in 2025.
>> I [music] see. I started gaming in 2025
only.
>> I was not interested in games at all.
>> Go ahead. Go ahead.
>> In 2025, my most favorite
OBS.
>> Yeah, it keeps on happening that I'm
only streaming on Twitch now. The
YouTube thing is constantly happening
that and I'm not streaming on YouTube no
more. The Twitch is active. Twitch is
going fine.
>> I think Twitch
>> maybe
it's more streamer friendly. I guess
>> might know more than me though.
>> Okay.
favorite God of War or Ragnarok
of War.
[snorts]
>> Oh.
>> Oh,
>> nice.
>> Okay.
>> I didn't even play it on stream.
Oh,
[laughter]
okay. You completed [music] it off
screen.
>> Okay. Happen. Okay.
>> Happens. Happens.
>> So, uh, who were the best people you
guys met this year?
>> Uh,
>> tell [music] me.
I I think I'll start on this one.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, first of all, it was
Joknix himself. I'm really happy for
this collab. I was looking forward to it
as well because favorite people are in
the chat like I am in call with them who
I met this year at at least met and
connected. as you guys are met. It was
really fun with Mo. Um the remember the
group thingy we we wanted to start then
we met Azu and yeah I would say it was a
blessing this year. I met many great
people this year. A lot of things
happened but yeah
>> same for me too. What about Kaid?
I met I met Mo just because of uh
just because of jock.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, [laughter]
>> wait. Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Any other people?
>> That that's how I met Surya Azu and
other people.
>> Why?
>> Yeah. Why the source
>> right now? My
>> Miko is the like center point.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh me uh [laughter] Okay.
This year, this year I met a lot of
people.
>> No.
>> Uh [clears throat] yeah, this year I met
a lot of people. Uh I met Yeah, I met
Sidia again. Reconnected with Yes. Then
Ka then
>> I met um I met Yeah, most of there were
like a lot of new YouTubers.
Um new YouTubers were there. Uh
oh, wait. Uh and also older one. No,
this year I think.
>> H Yeah, this year I think um yeah, Azan
was I think I talked with her. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
>> And uh and uh yeah, a lot of people then
my stuff have bad stuff happened and I
think I lost some people but it's all
right. Then I found a lot of good
creators I was watching. They were
really nice. I would love to be friends
with them.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. For me, it has to be you all. All
all the YouTubers I have met till now.
And my server people, I have my Discord
server. They have been the best [music]
for me. One of my best years. Okay. When
I met people, Nerf, she has been really
special for me. She has like she's like
my big sister and Yeah.
Oh, by the way,
uh like [music] we have been streaming
since 52 minutes.
[laughter]
>> Yeah,
my is almost over.
>> Oh, no. Oh, yeah. You have to go soon,
right?
>> Okay. When one last question from my
side, then if [music] you guys want to
continue and then I'll leave. Okay.
So what are your goals that you want to
continue for 2026
you want to fulfill it?
>> Sorry I I missed it. Can you repeat that
question for me please?
>> Uh what goals you have to complete in
2026?
Uh
>> I'm not the one speaking first.
What?
>> Okay. Uh, goals, goals, goals, goals.
Maybe
>> maybe 1k this year if I can. And maybe I
I need some active people for my
Discord, I guess.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, those [music] two.
>> Okay. And uh uh Kaid you
>> uh at least improve my memory and
[music] uh improve on YouTubing cuz uh
you know my memory got worse because of
some medication.
So I forgot forget things easily
>> like 5 minutes 10 minutes.
That's why I said
>> I want to improve I want to improve my
[music] memory.
>> Yeah. And job next to you.
>> Uh for me uh
for me I think I would like to focus on
IRL cuz I'll be going after two months
now like I only have till March for
going to Japan.
I I I hope I can stream from Japan. It
will be hard. Uh probably it will take
me uh after 6 months or something, but
I'll try to fight for it. Maybe. I I
don't know [laughter] cuz streaming is
fun. No, I would like to u do my best uh
with a content and everything. Make
vlogs maybe. That would be nice.
Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. [music] Okay. Okay. On me.
Uh, I have a specific goal
on [music] like like get more audience
on my Twitch and YouTube and continue
tubing since I have my boards this year
and I want to excel in them too. It's my
last year.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> It's not the multitasking. It's more
like God provide us like with power to
multitask.
>> Okay. It was fun being with you people
like I enjoyed this. Okay.
>> Thank you. Thank you for
having this. Okay. So, yeah.
>> I'll see you guys later.
>> Take care.
>> Thank you for inviting us. Have a great
year.
Happy new year everyone. [laughter]
>> I hope
>> so. Are you guys still
>> Go ahead. USA.
>> I was just saying like uh there's a lot
of uh tension. The last year was a f
pill of tension filled to the brim. This
I I really [music] hope this will be a
peaceful year like an uneventful
year. Hopefully
>> that's all. [music]
>> Yeah.
>> But what were you saying?
I was saying I I not just noticed
Syria's YouTube stream just died. So I
was like, "Oh no."
>> Yeah. Yeah. It it died like a lot. Uh
but yeah, every time I tried to like
restart the stream, it just uh my OBS
[music] just shut down for some reason.
>> And I was like, then I'll only run the
Twitch, I guess.
>> It's okay. It happens.
>> I'm just here. My stream is sobbed.
>> Oh, no. It's okay. [laughter]
>> Yeah. OBS is like OBS has an agenda
today. He's not going to let stream
anyone today. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, good. And YouTube too. Today it
didn't let Kayan like make the stream.
It like showed an error three or four
times. No. Why?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my god.
>> It's like that only. And that sometimes
when there's OBS that gives problem
sometime YouTube and then there's that
electricity guy who really likes to play
with his switches and he just turn on on
and off on and off like every 10 to 20
minutes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. At least if you want to like
let go of the electricity, let go for
like 2 to 3 hours. Don't just do like
every 30 minutes.
>> Exactly.
the power guy. [laughter]
>> He he he is the most cursed guy I guess
in India. Like every everyone curses him
a lot. [laughter]
>> Do you like call the person and ask when
will the lights come back? What do they
say? Did they not take the phone?
>> Yeah, I actually it it has actually
happened with me. I what happened was
after two reports like from the app
right I called him the third time I
called him the fourth time after the
fifth time he stopped the like picking
up the call
like I like I was at that point I was
like dude listen just cut off the light
don't give me hope okay just cut it off
>> same happened same happened here
>> oh my god
>> but now but Now it but now it doesn't
goes.
>> Yeah. And now it's like uh winters now.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. In summers they just like they are
really fearful of like I think
meditating it. I think the issue
>> whole day whole night.
>> Yeah. M
>> uh like after the April of la this last
year I think now it's called last year
after April March I don't think I have
any any issue with blackouts anymore.
>> Ah
>> yes
>> too accustomed to it being inside the
house too accustomed to be in blackouts
every time.
Uh I think it made us stronger uh 2025.
>> Yeah.
>> In one way or another.
>> Yep.
>> I don't care if I don't care if light
goes but ki
>> Oh yeah.
>> Yeah.
That's also another one.
It's just Yeah. It's a good recap if I'm
being honest.
Sitting with the everyone and having a
calm simple chat. It was possible. I am
still in the office for the audience.
[laughter]
If there was anyone in the background, I
apologize. People are coming and going
and I am talking in action with them to
keep quiet.
>> Hello Amido Sansa. Happy new year.
>> Happy new year.
>> How can I improve my English? I don't
know. just uh just watch movies and try
shadowing and stuff. It will help I
guess.
>> By the way, like are there any [music]
covers coming from your next place here?
Like I know you are into the music and
all that.
>> Uh okay. Honestly speaking, um I got
dragged. I was told to study this cover
song from that Chainsaw Man movie. No.
Uh Jane, no. Was it Jane Do? Uh yeah,
Jane Do. Yeah, I was told to learn a
Jane do song. It's a duet song. No. So
the main lines are like eight lines or
something. So I've been trying to learn
that. It is hard cuz I don't have I
don't know singing properly. Yeah, I
feel like
>> Mhm.
>> uh self study will get you like uh like
somewhere but you have to
uh like go through
>> mentor to like really learn how to do
everything now.
>> Mhm. But here in India,
>> yeah, uh you say I'll just finish my So
>> here in India, uh you don't you won't
get uh trainers who are into Japanese
music and stuff now. So I thought if I
can possibly next year or something or
yeah this year 2026
if I um if I can like save up I can try
to go through a vocal coach or something
in Japan maybe
that'll be
>> hopefully
>> I I hope it's not expensive. I think
that it's expensive, but I'll save up
and Yeah.
>> It will be a heavy thing on your pocket,
I guess, this year.
>> Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> What about you, K? Any covers from you?
>> I don't think in this year.
>> Happy New Year.
By the next
>> Yeah.
>> All of you guys are Indians. Yeah. and
the other one who was here uh earlier
Mikos
>> all of them are Indian YouTubers so
>> I don't know but
on my own but I don't think I I will
[music]
learn properly
but yeah I have I have hope
>> you have everyone [music] has hope this
year hopefully
>> it's a new year
>> there's also
yeah new to your new us, I guess.
[laughter]
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> You were saying
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. What was I saying?
>> Yeah. You were saying also then
something something.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh oh. I was I think I was
going to uh talk about the
content differentiation this year. No,
because we all going to need we all as a
as we are type of the community who will
not stick to one game, right?
>> We are going to go to different games
and the whole thing is about us as a
character, I think, not the game itself.
So you can't just go into the niche of
one way. How any ideas or any advice
this year that can help you achieve
[music] that goals
>> of like content stuff?
>> Yep. Yep. Like how can you like any
advice for yourself this year that you
think would be helpful? Well, I would
say for me
uh I've been always someone who was
scared to post stuff now because of the
lack of quality and stuff. I will be
like I don't have resources even for
covers as well. I I'll be like I don't
have anyone who can mix it for me or
make a music video this and that. No,
there will be always that excuses we all
make saying oh this won't work this and
that won't work this and that but
>> I would say when it comes to content for
myself
uh all these years I start I've been uh
like playing games doing variety this
and that now for this year 2026 I would
like to focus on content uh like how do
I say But um there are types of creators
who would look at the analytics and what
are the trends and everything. No, I was
always the type who didn't care about
the numbers and look at what's trending.
Whatever game I feel like playing, I'll
just play it. No. So this time
>> uh I would like to like take a like a a
step forward and try to see what all
like content can I make which are
trending and stuff. If it works out then
it's good but the main goal I would like
to have is finding what am I what what
type of content I enjoy the most you
know that's the main thing. Yeah.
[music]
>> Yeah. You don't want to force it or make
it fake.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What about you, P?
>> Uh
myself. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
>> Play any single game.
>> Are you all learning Japanese? I believe
I'm the only one.
>> Play a single game to grow like one
popular.
>> Hello, Real Studios. Happy New Year to
you guys as well. and do voice over uh
by scripting something funny and stuff
but
>> uh I felt like [music]
I will uh
do a commentary which I which I'm
feeling right
>> uh I play that game only which I want to
play even if it's not in trend
>> some people say I
>> should play only that game that is in
trend to uh grow but I don't think I
should this
>> uh
>> yeah this is a uh like I said this is a
challenge if you want to grow do you
want to be in the trend or do you want
to take an audience who likes you not
the game I think
>> like I don't really like this kind of
people's who just say uh I will like if
[music] You play this game or that game.
>> Ah yeah.
>> Like you just like you just walk away.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> It would be better now if people watch
you for you rather than the game or the
content. No.
>> Yeah.
>> That's the hopeful best outcome with
YouTube.
>> Yeah.
>> Then the algorithm
I feel like uh never seen a YouTuber
like uh my thinking. [music] Uh I think
in a deep way and uh different way which
I don't think it's related to video
tubing stuff but I want to be YouTuber.
So I think I'm uni unique one [music]
with the unique thinking. Uh so that's
why I think I won't get any much
audience.
Uh but I think if it's less it's enough
for me.
>> Uh if if they understand me that's
enough. [music]
>> Agreed. Agreed. The word of truth I
guess
the Yeah. Everyone's been unique in
their own. I cannot like there are a lot
of like people like now in the YouTubers
uh what we [music] can say is now in the
YouTuber industry you will find people
uh who have their who have used their
face cam as well who will use the model
as well on the same channel. So I I
think the boundary lines of a YouTuber
has thinned a lot.
>> Yeah.
like the line has been thinning [music]
uh slowly and steadily.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's good.
>> And there's a lot of like new creators.
[music]
>> Yeah.
>> People should be uh who what they are.
>> Yep.
>> True. True.
>> Right. True. There's also a lot of new
[music] like now that the animation
there are a lot of animators who were
working with YouTube animators coming to
the YouTube now themselves. So there's a
new batch of animators, new batch of
YouTubers and I would say 2026 would be
like a full of content. There would be
new stories, new people and yeah
>> hopefully everyone has a good time. Does
YouTube have a what was the thing that
trend was there? No, YouTube recycle.
No, recycle YouTube uh that like a year
thing yearly thingy. Ah, rewind. Is
there a rewind?
>> Yeah, I saw that. I saw that.
>> Was there a rewind for this year or did
they stop doing the rewind with a lot of
creators?
>> I think they stopped. I think they
stopped because of
uh that creators make them now. Uh
YouTube doesn't, I guess. Oh,
>> because I think the last one was
who who made that? Did YouTube made
that? YouTube used to make that, I
guess. Right.
>> Yeah, YouTube makes it. Uh, I think
>> Yeah, YouTube Rewind channel.
>> Uh, I don't Yeah, I don't see one
currently [music] on the YouTube. Yeah,
>> I think something happened after the
beast one. Mr. Beast one I think who
made that after YouTube and after that
one a lot of criticism happened and
after that there wasn't many.
>> Oh yeah Mr. Beast is 2020. Oh
>> yeah after that I think it stopped.
>> Wow.
Well, hopefully we get [music] to see a
new new setups and everyone grows into
like their own uniqueness, I would say.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
So, if you guys allow me, I would like
to take a step back and and my stream as
well and we can I can call it a day
because now there is a uh office worker
with me. I have to guide him.
>> Hi.
>> Good luck.
>> Happy new year.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey guys,
>> happy new year.
>> See you. Take care. Happy new year.
>> Yeah,
>> happy new year. Thanks for being Thanks
for making me part of this. Really
thankful [music] for the stream as well.
>> Thank you.
>> Hello.
>> Thank you guys.
>> Bye. Bye.
>> Hi. Bye.
See youa everyone.
>> I have to also go. I have to also go
because
>> Hi.
>> Uh I haven't did lunch.
>> Yeah. So
I think I should go too.
>> Uh
>> thank you for having me. It was a great
time.
>> Happy New Year.
See youa.
>> Happy new year.
>> I hope you enjoy this year.
>> Yeah, you too.
>> Hi.
Bye-bye.
>> Bye. See you.
>> Okay, that was everyone. [laughter]
I'll have to also wrap up, I guess. I
mean, I can't go on.
But um it was a collab. No. So don't
worry, I'll make a new stream. Um I
didn't wanted to like make a um a new
year thingy. Yeah. But yeah, how's
everyone? How's everyone's new year
been? Uh I believe um it's new year for
everyone all over the world, I guess. Uh
only a few places it's not new year yet.
So
uh hello Aan hello.
Uh but I'm sure I will pass. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh for JP. No it will take a while for
results. For NAT you get to know by
three or four days. Yeah.
And also uh I was I just wanted to uh uh
I just wanted to uh let you like how do
I say I forgot English. Wow. So, all the
collab partners for today's stream of
their links are in the description down
below. If you feel like checking them
out, they are really really wonderful
creators. Uh, and um they were like a
good friend to me. So, I'm really happy
that uh they all invited me to hang out
with them. So,
feel free to follow them if you like. It
would really mean a lot. The links are
in the description. Hi,
nice.
[gasps]
[sighs] Um,
hello Mikosan. Hi feel. Oh, thank you
for coming from your YouTube channel.
Okay, I'll support you.
[gasps]
Wow, you made a lot of cording streams
and Oh, entry stuff. Nice.
Oh, nice. Nice.
Really nice. Good. Good.
Eat lunch. Ah, yeah. Yeah. I was
actually eating lunch uh my lunch while
we were
while we were doing the collab stuff.
I actually bought a uh like took the
plate upstairs.
[laughter]
No one saw me carrying my food. uh like
people who were passing by from the
roadside. No, no one saw it. I just
quickly speedrun and came up here to my
office room thingy and I put it here and
when we started our stream and slowly
started to eat.
Uh do you remember? Of course I remember
you. Did you forget you came by when I
was learning Japanese? Uh it was the end
the time I was doing the kanji stream.
Right. Yeah. At the time I was doing the
[snorts] uh kanji stream and um yeah you
came by that time. Yes.
Yeah. Who is Miko Money? Uh Miko Bunny
was uh is a Indian YouTuber. Mikos was
there with us during this collab in the
beginning. So, Mikosa was uh the host
for this collab [music] this new year.
Uh like a it's like a party you can say
or like a hangout with friends,
celebration with friends where we talked
about how our 2025 went and [music]
um how um what we are expecting for 2026
and stuff
all the fun stuff. Yeah, Mikosa is a
YouTuber as well. Although check them
out if you like. The links to Mikosan
will be in the description.
Yeah, Mikosan streams on YouTube. No,
YouTube. So, so
yeah, I was doing N5. Yeah, my uh NAT uh
my NAT Q4 exam is on January 18th. So, I
have to study, bro. I have to study. My
offline classes will be like this week.
Uh January this week. Yeah. For five. Um
yeah, I have like how many days? Uh 18th
is Sunday. 18th is Sunday. So I have to
travel so far to write the exam. So 16
17 18 19 I won't be streaming.
Uh but the 24x7 channel will be uh
there. Uh the 24 channel will be
running. So if you wish to if you want
to get your daily jose of jockn you can
just watch the 24x7 channels always on
channels. My PC will be on whenever when
I'm away from home. I'll just control
it. I'll have everything automated. Even
if a power cut happens, [laughter] I'll
ask someone to turn it on or I'll
somehow turn it on remotely from my
phone and like
uh yeah, and whenever it boots up the
PC, it'll automatically start OBS and
start streaming. So, it's fine.
Um
uh N4 is easy. Yeah. Yeah. Uh I have to
do the like anki anki and the trien for.
So yeah
my only weakness is kanji. I have to
slowly practice and practice on kanji.
Kanji kun. I have to practice kanji kun.
Yeah.
[snorts] Also, speaking of kanjis and
everything, um, and it's kind of off
topic, but yeah, I uh made a video about
my 2025X stuff, how my year recap is.
It's a long video. If you would love to
re watch it, feel free to watch it. Or
if you don't want to watch it, it's all
good. You can always summarize it.
There's like a summarize feature, right?
Uh Germany Google Germany AI is there in
YouTube. So you can just click on that
and and like um [laughter] I didn't know
I recently discovered it. You can
summarize a video without watching it.
It has everything. How much you got in
NI? I'm not sure. I didn't get the email
from uh the NATE people NAT exam thingy.
I was supposed to get it but I think I
did not get it. Um I did not get it I
believe. Um but I did pass. I did
finally out and five it's Q5. I never
did JPT. I did that.
So then
so uh it is going to be 4:00 p.m. I will
uh wrap the stream up this collab stream
up uh cuz our collab partners have ended
their stream. Uh it's way better. I will
start a new stream later uh tonight.
Today uh that'll be better so we can
just have a talk or something all those
stuff. Okay. [snorts] And uh play games
or something. Yeah. I I haven't touched
our creators, so I would love to uh play
Arc Raiders then. Yeah.
So done it. Also got to eat. [laughter]
Yeah.
Honestly, yesterday I was supposed to do
the countdown stream
like counting down to New Year and
stuff. No, we used to do that all these
years. And I slept off, man. I slept
like a a lo like a a log, I guess. I
slept from 7 or 8:00 p.m. till
4 a.m.
My parents, they I didn't eat dinner. I
slept off. That's it. I slept off and
[laughter] woke up late.
[gasps]
Wow.
Hello, young professionals. Welcome. um
stream. Yeah, I couldn't do it this
year. It's okay. I at least did the
video now. Yeah, I didn't want to do a
stream um because my video was rendering
so it took uh too long.
But yeah,
damn, your English is so good. My
English I don't know. I you know I suck
at English.
The thing is now what I did was when I
started my streaming thingy I was so bad
at English. I never spoke with anyone.
No. So what I did was every stream I do
I took like a challenge like yeah this
stream I'm going to speak for 10 minutes
or 5 minutes. I have to speak in English
proper sentences or challenge myself.
No. So I started to
uh do the thing like every stream kept
the goal I will speak for 10 minutes I
will speak for 20 minutes if I am able
to fulfill the goal 10 minutes if I can
speak for 10 minutes without making a
mistake without uh struggling then I
make it 20 minutes like that slowly
slowly slowly over the years I was able
to get my English okayish
yeah I would say A good advice would be
to uh watch English creative, watch
English movies,
consume English content, the media wise.
Now that's the same advice now people
give you when when it comes to learning
a language like Japanese as well.
Consume the media, right? And don't just
consume it for entertainment, but look
at how the sentence formation is and
everything, right? Yeah. Um how and why
a sentence is uh mentioned like that?
Why did the person like structure their
sentence like that? All those stuff. No.
Yeah. Do that and uh slowly slowly
you'll be able to
speak and then the next thing is
um then the next thing is thinking in
English. No, you'll be automatically
thinking in your native language, right?
But you'll slowly start to slowly slowly
start to think on the language you are
learning. That's the same advice uh with
Japanese. Now,
are you teaching? No, no, no. I was
giving an advice thingy. Um
uh uh there was a person on YouTube who
was asking about English, how to get
improve in English like that. Hello for
your answers and happy new year.
For me, learning Japanese is way easier
than English, but I will try. Oh, yeah.
If that's the case, then uh uh try to
translate Japanese to English kind of
thing. You know, you'll be thinking in
Japanese first, right? I believe uh
you're you you have like uh like trained
yourself to
um like think first in Japanese right
now, right? Yeah. Slowly slowly watch
English movies this and that. Yeah. And
you can try doing shadowing
like or like sing like listening to
songs and stuff. No, that that would
also work.
Also do Anki space uh repetitive
uh stuff, right? Like that that is
really good.
And one YouTube channel I will recommend
uh which gives a lot of advice on
uh
oh like speaking and public speaking and
stuff is if I can find it. One second
let me find it.
Uh
yeah, this channel when Yeah. Ask. Yeah.
Yeah. This channel. Let me give you
Yeah. Yeah. This channel is really good.
It tells you how to speak, how to like
let people hear you. This is a good
channel. You can watch it. Um,
yeah. Yeah. The only way to get better
is actually speaking in English. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. True, true, true.
Watch out. Taking advice. [laughter]
Happy New Year for your friends.
I want to also master Japanese man.
It'll take time.
Sure. Sure.
But yeah,
I know him
publicly speaking is part of what I do
for a living. So [laughter]
sure and I also should take public
speaking go stuff like start practicing
it. Yeah, I suck at that. I have to
learn.
So then anyway, it's going to be 4:00 p.
p.m. I'll wrap up this stream cuz this
is a collab stream, right? I should not
uh overtake this collab stream. Like uh
I mean I could it's fine, but I don't
want to I want so I don't I want it so
that people can watch back on this
collab stream if they want. So yeah, uh
since the collab has ended, yeah, we we
will do our I will do a solo stream
after this uh by like a few hours, I
guess 6:00 p.m. or something. I'll play
a game or just chat or just do variety,
I guess. So don't worry about that.
Might overlap with my stream. Oh, you're
also streaming for your answer.
Wow.
Oh yeah, you got to do your new year
stream now. Good luck. Good luck. But
you started streaming,
Ben. Wait. Oh, wait. Oh, yeah. You did
start streaming. What?
Is going by. Hi. Take care. Take care.
Thank you for coming by.
Thank you for coming by. Have a good
good
new year ahead and enjoy yourself. Good
luck.
Like a few weeks ago. Ah,
I've been so out of date with everyone,
man.
Yeah,
I've been so out of date with everyone.
I've been only
I haven't even talked with anyone.
I uh
I haven't even wished anyone happy new
year. [laughter]
Only the people who DM'd me. I I I I'm
usually the type to send everyone happy
new year. But yeah, now I can't do kind
of like that stuff now
cuz I don't know who are still talking
with me, who are still connected with me
anymore. So there's that.
But yeah,
today was nice. I enjoyed it.
Okay, it is time to wrap up. We'll we'll
start doing that.
Hello, M. Happy New Year. Happy New
Year. You're late. I'm going to wrap up
the stream. [laughter]
It's okay. [music] Happy New Year, M.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year. Thank you for coming by.
I think I saw your stream. Did you
stream yesterday? I think I think you
did. I believe
uh Assas was streaming. So
yeah,
I got notification on that. [laughter]
Oh, you didn't. Ah. Oh, I think I was
watching the world of us. Then I think I
saw you there. Yeah, maybe that.
But yeah, thank you for coming. I'm
going to wrap up this stream cuz it was
a collab stream. No.
Um,
I will be doing my solo stream by 6:00
p.m. I haven't scheduled it, but yeah, I
think this year I'll start doing like a
No, no, I should not do the stream
schedule. I only have two months then. I
only have January and February. That's
it. I mean January, February, March.
So
my god [laughter]
see if I stay that is wait you didn't
sleep
did you not sleep you moving uh Japan
stuff right that's happening on April
that's happening on April and
yeah yeah yeah I will get my COE by
February
[sighs and gasps]
if nothing happens. If uh if everything
goes well, it's good. I have my exams on
January 18th.
I have to study for the Japanese exam. I
have to go to Chennai and
uh [laughter]
right
it'll be nice to visit Chennai again.
It's like a different culture there.
[laughter]
Everything is so different. Wow.
After M's child will be gone, I don't
want to leave. But I also want to leave.
Yeah, [laughter]
it is what it is.
Anyway, I will wrap it up over here.
We'll see you guys
uh on the 6 p.m. stream.
Honestly speaking, if I'm going to
stream Arc Raiders, it's way better if I
do it off stream cuz I have luck off
stream rather than streaming on stream.
[laughter]
[gasps]
I've been broke there. But yeah,
but more famous all the time. Yeah. Hi.
I'll wrap up. Okay. Hi. See you guys on
6 p.m. or later tonight's stream. Okay.
Hi.
Thank you to all who came by today on
this stream. [music] And thank you to
Mikosa for inviting me to this collab
with Nimikosan
and Suryak and Kisan. Thank you. Thank
you to all. [music] Special thank you to
all three of them for inviting